Dearest Guinevere,
It has been ages since I last had the honor of resting mine eyes upon your heavenly eyes. The sparkle like all the stars in the sky distilled into the finest of wines, of which I have oft supped upon, as I gaze wistfully out my window at your manor. Forgive me if this is too forward, but what else shall I do? The winter of my soul melts under the radiance of your delicate flower, and with your affections an entire field of wonder will sprout and grow towards your golden locks, like sunflowers in the field turning towards the blissful sun. You must know how I wish to join you one lovely evening, to curl ourselves around each other, to get in from the dreadful storm that seems to plague my mind whenever we are apart like this. Please respond post-haste, as I will anxiously await your response with baited breath, for then I can fly like a freed sparrow to your window.
Yours forever,
Alexander Princeton of Dukington, the third
